nowtoronto.com 2012-10-28

# Privacy policy | NOW Magazine

## Privacy Policy Statement

This is the web site of NOW Magazine, owned and operated by NOW Communications Inc.

Our postal address is: 189 Church Street, Toronto, Ontario, M4K 1Y7

We can be reached via e-mail at [newmedia@nowtoronto.com](mailto:newmedia@nowtoronto.com) or you can reach us by telephone at 416-364-1300

NOW respects the privacy of all of its users and is committed to protecting such privacy in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy explains NOW 's treatment of your personally identifiable information collected in connection with your activities on or related to all NOW websites referencing this Privacy Policy (the "NOW Sites") and all services made available on the NOW Sites (collectively, unless noted otherwise, the "NOW Services"). This Privacy Policy also explains how you can ask questions and make suggestions about our privacy practices and review and update your personal information.

We urge you to read this Privacy Policy carefully and to check back periodically as this Privacy Policy may change form time to time. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies or websites which are not owned or controlled by NOW.

## Information Collected

In the course of operating the NOW Services, we may collect two types of information about our users: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information.

"Personal Information" is personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, birth date and gender. Personal Information is collected by us when you choose to provide it to us when registering for a NOW Service, such as when you choose to subscribe to a NOW Service, enter a NOW promotion or choose to receive a NOW newspaper. In addition, if you choose to contact any of our customer service representatives, we may keep a record of that correspondence so that we may fully address the subject matter. We may also receive Personal Information from our business partners and other third parties, provided that such third parties confirm to us that you have permitted them to share such information.

Business contact information such as the name, title, business address, email address or telephone number of a business or professional person or an employee of an organization is not considered Personal Information.

"Non-Personal Information" is information of an anonymous nature, such as an Internet Protocol Address (IP Address), the domain used to access a NOW Service, and the type and version of browser or operating system being used. Aggregate information, such as demographic statistics of our users (e.g. average age or geographical allocation of our users), number of visitors and average time spent on a NOW Service, is also considered Non-Personal Information.

Non-Personal Information is collected or derived by us in the course of operating the NOW Services. For example, our Web servers may automatically collect Non-Personal Information which is provided through your browser or stored on a Cookie when you choose to visit a NOW Service.

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name and e-mail address (where possible). This information is not collected for any use other than to troubleshoot problems with the web server and keep statistics.

We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations and the IP address of contest entrants in order to track entries and ensure that entrants only submit once per contest.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page and only used to contact our users who have requested us to do so via opt-in mailing lists.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads and track contest entries so as to prevent duplicate submissions.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by e-mailing [newmedia@nowtoronto.com](mailto:newmedia@nowtoronto.com).

## Disclosure Of Personal Information

We will not sell or rent your Personal Information to anyone. We will only disclose your Personal Information to third parties:

  * Where you have specifically given us your consent to disclose your Personal Information for a designated purpose;
  * Who are acting on our behalf as our agents, suppliers or service providers, solely to enable us to more efficiently provide you with the NOW Services. Such entities act under strict contractual controls, requiring them to maintain the confidentiality of all such Personal Information and to use such information solely for purposes related to the provision of the NOW Services; 
  * As may be set out in the Terms and Conditions applicable to a NOW Service, to facilitate the provision of such NOW Service, such as fulfilling legal requirements; 
  * As required by law, including by an order of any court, institution or body with jurisdiction or authority to compel the production of information, or in order to protect or defend a legal interest; or 
  * In connection with a NOW corporate re-organization, merger or amalgamation with another entity, or a sale of all or a substantial portion of the assets of NOW provided that the Personal Information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy by the entity acquiring the information.

From time to time, we make the e-mail addresses of those who access our site available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. This is only done so on an opt-in basis or when otherwise specified. Persons entering contests are informed through the rules that all information submitted becomes property of NOW Communications Inc and the Sponsor where applicable. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by emailing us at the number provided above. You will never receive any unsolicited post mail from us. Postal codes are only collected for the purposes of demographic information and for contests as a tool to keep track of entrants.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line or are only required to do so for the purposes of entering contests and will only be contacted by telephone upon winning said contest if applicable.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. 

## Links To Other Sites And Advertisements

A NOW Service may contain links to other websites and services. While we try to link only to sites and services that share our high standards and respect for privacy, please understand that we are not responsible for the content of, or the privacy practices employed by, other companies or websites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the NOW Services referencing this Privacy Policy.

The majority of the advertisements which are displayed in connection with the NOW Services are served through a reputable third party advertisement serving partner. If you would like to know more about what Non-Personal Information is collected and how information is used by our partner or about its "opt-out" procedures, please click here

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. NOW takes technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps to protect Personal Information that you provide to us. We instruct our employees with access to your Personal Information that it is to be used only in adherence with the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy and the laws applicable to each specific business.

In certain areas, such as when you provide credit card information to us, we work to help protect the security of your credit card information during transmission by using industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology.

You can help protect the security of your Personal Information as well. For instance, never give out your password, since this is what is used to access your Account or Registration Information. Also remember to log out of your account and close your browser window when you finish using a NOW Service or surfing the Web, so that other people using the same computer won't have access to your information.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

NOW may from time to time change its Privacy Policy as new NOW Services are added or old ones changed. Changes will be effective when notice of such change is posted at a NOW Site. Please check this Privacy Policy regularly for updates by checking the date of "Last Update" at the top of this document.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
